

Muhammed Fasil C U

Senior Software Engineer | Full Stack Developer

Highly-skilled and motivated senior software engineer with 5+ years of experience. Proven skills in full stack development and working as a Senior Software Engineer at Quest Global Pvt.Ltd.

 \times

mfasilcu@gmail.com

+91 90 20 022 719

in linkedin.com/in/muhammedfasilcu/

& Eranakulam, India

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer QuEST Global Engineering Pvt.Ltd

12-2018 - Present

Trivandrum, India

QuEST Global (formely Quality Engineering and Software Technologies) is a product engineering company in the Aero engines, Aerospace & Defense, Hi-Tech and Industrial, Medical devices, Oil & Gas, Power and Transportation verticals.

Technology Innovation Fellow Kerala Start-up Mission

05-2017 - 04-2018

Trivandrum.India

KSUM (Kerala Start-up Mission) is the central agency of the Government of Kerala for entrepreneurship development and incubation activities in Kerala, India.

Software Engineer - Android Developer Q10 Technologies Pvt.Ltd

05-2015 - 04-2017

Cochin, India

Q10 Technologies is a niche technology studio founded by a team having rich experience in managing, developing, implementing and integrating enterprise software solutions.

EDUCATION

Professional Engineer - Computer Application The Institution of Engineers, India

05-2018 - Pursuing

Diploma in Computer Application Technical Education Board, Kerala

05-2012 - 03-2015

LANGUAGES

English

Malayalam

INTERESTS

Reading

Travelling

SKILLS

JAVA 8

Spring boot

Android

Angular

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

OMNI - PET-CT Scanner

GE - Healthcare

Client - Haifa, Israel

OMNI - PET-CT Scanner is a scanning device for an imaging test that can help reveal the metabolic or biochemical function of your tissues and organs.

Project role and responsibilities

- Detailed analysis of medical devices and system requirements
- Preparing of Technical design review document based on SSRS
- Designing of user interface according to the requirement
- Developing different modules of software based on the approved design
- Guiding junior developers to deliver quality products

BookByQ

Q10 Technologies

BookbyQ is a ticket booking platform for Movies and Events across Kerala

Project role and responsibilities

- Detailed analysis of requirement and design development
- Developing an end to end mobile application based on the design

HONOR AWARDS

haQathon

QuEST Global Engineering Pvt.Ltd

- Technology excellence

